8미리 2
무죄!
Not guilty!
법원 속기사와 한다고?
So you were fucking the court stenographer.
법원 속기사와 하는
공상을 한다는 거지
I was just fantasizing
I was fucking the court stenographer.
- 난 별로 안 내키네
- 환상을 얘기해 달라면서
- Not sure I like that, David.
- It was you who started this fantasy game.
그래, 당신은
환상에 빠져서 사네
Yeah, and you seem to have mastered it.
대사관의 참사관이
법원에서 하고 싶다는 걸...
I wonder what my father would say
if he knew an embassy counselor...
아빠가 아시 면 뭐라고 하실까?
was fantasizing sex in the courtroom?
대사님도 분명
성적 환상이 있으셨을 거야
I'm sure the Ambassador has had
a few carnal thoughts in his lifetime.
상견례할 때
직접 물어보지 그래?
Why don't you ask him
at our little wedding-planning dinner?
그건 안 돼, 티쉬
I don't think so, Tish.
꽤...
It's...
흥미롭네
interesting.
알람브라에 잘 오셨습니다
Welcome to the Alhambra.
관리인은 해가 지면 퇴근합니다
The housekeepers leave at sunset.
보시다시피 겨울엔
손님이 별로 없죠
As you can see,
we have very few guests in winter.
아침 식사는
오전 7~10시입니다
Breakfast is served 7:00 to 10:00.
점심, 저녁은 없지만
훌륭한 식당이...
No lunch or dinner,
but you will find excellent dining...
베즈프렘에 있습니다
in Veszprem.
생각보다 괜찮네
Wow. This is actually nice.
꽤 좋은데
Very nice.
온천은 밤까지 개장합니다
The baths are open until the night.
약간만 걸어가시면 되죠
They are a short walk from here.
전 조세프 클림입니다
My name is Josef Klim.
필요한 게 있으시면
언제든 연락하세요
Anything you need,
do not hesitate to call me.
'언제든 연락하세요'
"Do not hesitate to call me."
자기도 저 사람이 괴짜 같아?
Okay, is it just me,
or is the Klim guy just a little bit creepy?
짐을 풀까? 아니면...
So you wanna unpack or something?
아니면?
Or something, huh?
자기의 진짜 환상이 뭐야?
What really is your fantasy?
만약 이 세상에서...
I mean, if you could have...
하나만 가질 수 있다면...
one thing in the entire world...
뭘 갖고 싶어?
what would it be?
당신과 결혼하고
대통령에 당선되는 것
Marry you and get elected President.
그건 두 개잖아
That's two.
정치적 성공
당신은 이미 가졌잖아
Political success. I already have you.
농담 아니야
I'm serious.
바보 같은 얘기야
It's a silly game.
말해 봐
I want you to give me one...
꼭 나와 결혼해야 하는
이유를 말이야
really good reason
why you want to marry me.
첫째, 당신을 사랑해
One: I love you.
둘째, 평생을
당신과 함께하고 싶어
Two: I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
셋째, 세계 최고의
총각 파티를 할 수 있잖아
And three: I get to have the most awesome
bachelor party in the world.
친구라는 작자들이 준비한
그따위 유치한 놀이가...
I cannot understand
your complete obsession with this night...
왜 좋다고 하는지
이해를 못하겠어
of infantile debauchery that
your so-called friends have planned for you.
이리 와
Come here.
난 이제 그 유명하다는...
I want to go see...
온천에 갈 거야
these famous baths...
그 다음엔 돌아와서
화끈하게 즐기겠어
and then I want to come back here and fuck.
난 이의 없어
Sounds good to me.
'난 이의 없어'
"Sounds good to me."
자긴 정말 귀여워
You're so adorable.
총각 파티는 전통이야
You know, bachelor parties are a tradition.
- 멋진 전통이네
- 여자도 하잖아
- It's some tradition.
- Women have them, too.
그래, 린 언니도 난리야
배울 만큼 배운 사람들이...
Yeah, I know. Lynn's was absurd.
I mean, imagine 20 college-educated...
이런 세상에
My, my.
놀랍군
Incredible.
성질 돋구지 마
Don't push your luck.
- 난 그런 뜻이...
- 아니긴 뭐가 아냐
- Well, I only meant that...
- I know exactly what you meant.
누군지 궁금하군
I wonder who she is.
내려가서 물어보지 그래?
말동무가 필요해 보이는데
Why don't you go down there and ask her?
I'm sure she'd appreciate the intrusion.
어디 가?
Where you going?
벗은 여자나 보려고
여기까지 온 게 아냐
I didn't drive all this way
to stare at a naked woman.
저 정도면 그 정도 수고는
괜찮은 것 같은데
Well, it seems like
a perfectly good reason to me.
재밌네
That's funny.
사실을 말해봐
Tell me the truth.
아까 그 여자를 상상했지?
You were just thinking about that woman,
weren't you?
아냐
No.
거짓말
Liar.
좋아
Okay.
어머니 때문에 미치겠어
My mother is driving me crazy.
꼭 지금 해야겠어?
봄에 미국에 가서 할까?
You sure you want to do it now?
Or wait till the spring in the States?
내 앞에서 꼬리 내리지 마
Do not try to weasel out on me.
당신과 결혼하려고 여기까지 왔어
I came all the way here to get married...
긴 다리의 헝가리 여자에게
뺏기기 전에 말이야
before I lose you
to some long-legged Hungarian beauty.
봄에는 결혼 피로연을 하자
We can have the reception in the spring.
오늘밤은 뭘 하지?
What are we gonna do tonight?
아까 그 괴짜 친구가
식당을 추천하면서...
Your creepy little friend
recommended a restaurant in Veszprem...
물 좋은 클럽도 알려줬어
and told me about this great club.
거기 가자, 응?
Can we go, please?
그래, 또 그 여자 얘기도 들었어
Sure. He also told me about that girl.
무슨 여자?
What girl?
온천의 그 여자, 기억 나?
The one from the baths, remember?
당신은 잘도 기억하네
Obviously, you do.
우리 말고 이 호텔 손님은
그 여자뿐이래
He told me
that she's the only other guest in the hotel...
부다페스트에서 자주 온다더군
that she comes here frequently
from Budapest...
당신처럼 가족이
엄청나게 부자라더군
that she comes from a mega-rich family,
such as yourself...
게다가 모델이고...
and she's a model...
영화에도 출연했대
and she's done some film.
그 여자 신발 사이즈는
안 물어봤어?
Did you happen to get her shoe size
while you were at it?
- 그냥 얘기만 한 거야
- 말은 잘하셔
- I was just making conversation.
- Just making conversation.
술 한잔 해야겠어, 자기는?
I'm gonna go get a drink. Want one?
정말?
You sure?
오늘 오후...
This afternoon...
우리가 보는 걸 알고 있었죠?
you knew we were watching you,
didn't you?
당신과 남편?
You and your husband?
약혼자예요
Fiance.
전 리사예요
My name is Risa.
티쉬예요
Tish.
여긴 왜 왔죠?
So why did you come here?
춤추러요
To dance.
아니, 온천장에요
I mean here, to the baths.
기분전환이죠
To get away.
모험이죠
Have a little adventure.
그래서 모험을 했나요?
And have you had an adventure?
아뇨
Not really.
모험을 원하나요?
약혼자와 함께?
You want one? You and your fiance?
티쉬!
Hey!
데이빗!
David!
이쪽은 리사
Risa.
리사, 데이빗이에요
Risa, David.
제 가방을 가져오죠
I'll get my things.
무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
세계 최고의 총각 파티
선물이라고 생각해
Just think of it as the best fucking
bachelor party you'll ever have.
이유는 모르겠지만
갑자기 그러고 싶었어
I don't know why,
but I wanted to all of a sudden.
그만한 환상도 없잖아
It was better than any fantasy.
우린 미쳤어, 알아?
We're crazy, you know that?
사랑해
I love you.
알아
I know.
나도 사랑해
Me, too, to you.
왜 그들을 옹호하죠, 리처드?
How can you defend them, Richard?
옹호하는 게 아니라
자네 말에 동의하지 않는 거야
It's not about defending anyone.
I just don't agree with you.
백악관이 시민의 자유를
구속한다고 생각지 않아요?
You don't think the White House
is dismantling our civil liberties?
아니, 그렇게 생각 안 해
No, I don't think so.
손님들은 관심 없는 얘기야, 페리
Our guests aren't interested in this, Perry.
그럼 관심을 가져야지, 누나
우린 세계를 지배하잖아
Well, they should be, dear Sister.
What we do affects everyone.
우리가 뛰라면 세계가 되물어
'얼마나 높이요? ' 라고
When we say, "Jump,"
the rest of the world says, "How high?"
무례하구나
때와 장소를 가려야지
That was rude,
and this is not the time or the place.
뭐가 어때서?
Why not?
한말씀 하시죠, 자모스 씨?
What do you say, Mr. Szamos?
당신 조심해요
점프는 잘 못하잖아요
Careful, Tamas.
You are very bad at jumping.
요즘 같은 세상에
대통령의 첫 관심사는...
In these troubled times,
I would presume that safeguards...
안전이라고 생각하네
might be your President's first priority.
평소처럼 또 내 아들이
과장을 하는군요
As usual,
my son grossly exaggerates the issue.
누가 구속한다고 그래?
Nobody is dismantling anything.
조국의 안전을 위해
그 정도 대가는 감수해야지
It's a perfectly normal price to pay
for homeland security.
그들은 미국을 훔쳤어요
Please. They're stealing America...
반전, 임신 중절
동성애자를 지지하거나...
and God forbid if you're anti-war,
pro-choice, or gay...
하나님의 종이 아니라면
가만두지 않죠
or not one of their fanatical legions
of evangelical hand puppets.
그래, 가만두지 않지
Yes, God forbid.
사법권은 어때요?
What about the Judiciary?
지금 법정은...
Isn't anyone concerned...
마치 망할 우익들이 벌이는
만화 같지 않나요?
that it's being turned into
a goddamn right-wing dog-and-pony show?
페리, 말 조심해라
Perry. Language.
죄송해요, 어머니
어쨌든 우습잖아요
Sorry, Mother, but really, it's a joke.
그 웃기지도 않는
환경 정책도 마찬가지예요
Just like their slash-and-burn
environmental policies.
아들아, 넌 모르나 본데
에너지 문제가 심각하단다
Well, you may not have noticed, Son,
but there is an energy crisis...
백악관이 그걸
굳이 숨길 이유는 없어
and the White House
doesn't have to sugarcoat reality.
지금은 전쟁이야
We are at war...
나무가 더 중요하다는
네 사상은 이제 구닥다리야
and the world of your tree-hugging ideology
is passe...
증거도 없고 위험한 생각이지
and it is uninformed, and it is dangerous.
석유회사에겐 그렇겠죠
To the oil companies it is.
뭐라고?
Excuse me?
백악관이 화려한 미사여구로
거대 산업체라는...
Sometimes I think
it's just White House rhetoric...
지지기반을 숨겨주고
국민에게 겁을 주며...
masking conservative support
of big business...
석유 탐사를
정당화시키는 것 같습니다
designed to scare us into oil exploration.
그들의 모든 전략은
공포를 기반으로 하죠
Everything they're doing
is designed on fear.
공포라고?
Fear?
미국은 스스로의 그림자를
두려워하는 국가입니다
We're a nation scared of our own shadow.
어쩌다 이런 진보 공화당원이
자네 대사관의 참사관이 됐지?
How the hell did a liberal Republican
get appointed counselor in your embassy?
훌륭한 변호사니까요
He's a very fine lawyer, that's how.
게다가 대사의 딸과
그짓도 하잖아요
Not to mention he's screwing
the Ambassador's daughter.
그것도 아주 잘 하고 있죠
And doing it quite well, I might add.
창피한 줄 알아라, 티쉬
너도야, 페리
Shame on you, Tish. And you, too, Perry.
신경쓰지 마세요
Pay them no mind.
제 자식 중에 우아하고
상식이 있는 건 린 뿐이에요
Lynn is my only child
with any sense of grace and subtlety.
나머지 둘은 마치
남부 민주당원처럼 굴어요
These two act like Southern Democrats.
더 이상 아버지와는 말 못해
아무도 못할 거야
I can't talk to him, anymore. No one can.
- 난 엄마가 더 불쌍해
- 난 아냐
- It's Mother I feel sorry for.
- I don't.
인턴과 부적절한 관계가 있던
몇 년 전에 이혼하셨어야지
She should have left him years ago,
especially after that little intern thing.
어떻게 데이빗과 티쉬의 사생활을
그런 자리에서 말할 수 있어?
I can't believe you said that
about David and Tish at dinner tonight.
어떻게 어머니가 우리를
남부 민주당원과 비교할 수 있지?
I can't believe our dear mother
compared us to Southern Democrats.
다른 세상에 사시잖아
She lives in another world.
맞아, 엄마는 페리가
멋지다고 하시니까
No shit. She thinks Perry's just flamboyant.
퍽이나 재밌네!
Very funny!
아빠가 언짢아 하시던데
Well, Daddy wasn't amused.
항상 그렇잖아
He never is.
춤추실래요?
Would you like to dance?
전 결혼했어요
I'm married.
잘난 척 하지 마
내게 물어본 거야
Don't be a bitch. He meant me.
국무성에 소문이 돌고 있어
There's a rumor going around
that the State Department...
카라즈 채굴권 계약건 말이야
has made a decision
on the Karasz oil leases.
정신 차려, 리처드
절대 내게 맡기진 않아
Forget it, Richard,
they're not gonna give it to us.
좀 더 경험 있는 사람에게 맡기겠지
They're gonna give it
to someone with more experience.
바시 건이 꼬였던 건 알아
Look, I know the Vaci deal
didn't work out for you.
내 실수는 아니었어
It wasn't my fault.
자네 실수라는 게 아니라...
I'm not saying it was. It's just...
오늘 저녁에 했던 말이
불안하다 그거지
that comment
you made at dinner didn't help.
페리에게 하셨던 말씀을
참을 수가 없었을 뿐이야
I was just fed up with the way
he was hammering Perry all night.
그에게 덤빌 순 없어
장인어른은 왕이라고
And trust me on this, you can't hurt him.
He's the king.
가끔씩 왕에게 총을 쏴서...
Yeah, well, sometimes you gotta
take a shot at the king...
성 밖에 평민이 있다는 걸
깨닫게 해 줘야지
to remind him the peasants
are still out there.
그래, 평생 평민으로 남고 싶다면
Yeah, only if you want to remain a peasant.
이젠 가봐야겠어
내일 이민국 일이 있거든
I think I'm gonna call it a night.
I got immigration tomorrow.
그래, 난 오늘 부모님과 지내며
페리를 보호하겠어
Okay. I'm gonna stay with my parents
tonight and run interference for Perry.
- 보호자가 필요하니까
- 좋아
- Think he's gonna need it.
- Okay.
나중에 봐
Talk to you later.
- 잘 가요, 데이빗
- 사랑해!
- Night, David.
- Love you!
해롤드 심스가 카라즈 계약을
데이빗과 리처드에게...
So there's a rumor that Harold Simms
is pushing for David and Richard...
넘긴다는 소문이 있어
to get the Karasz oil leases.
정말?
Really?
데이빗이 국회로 진출하는
길이 될 수도 있어
This could be David's way
to a congressional seat.
백악관도 데이빗에게
신세를 지겠지
The White House would owe him.
알람브라가 어땠는지 궁금해
I wanted to ask how you guys
liked the Alhambra.
거기 온천이 끝내준다던데
I've heard the baths are unbelievable.
끝내줬지
Unbelievable.
무슨 일이야?
What happened?
카라즈 건을 우리가 맡았어
He gave us the Karasz oil leases.
근데 왜 똥 씹은 얼굴이야?
Then why do you look like
he just had your balls for lunch?
기대도 안했거든
I really wasn't expecting it.
- 안녕, 도라
- 안녕하세요
- Good morning, Dora.
- Good morning.
카라즈 건을 맡았어
We got the Karasz deal.
축하드려요!
Congratulations, sir!
다른 전화는 막아두고
티쉬를 연결해줘요
So hold all my calls
and get Tish on the line, please.
기다려
Hang on.
여보세요?
Yeah?
잠시만요
Hang on.
티쉬, 전화 왔어
Tish! Phone for you.
다시 전화할게
Can I call you back?
데이빗 전화야, 우리 늦었어
David's on the phone for you and we're late.
자기야, 무슨 일이야?
Hi, babe. What's up?
'카라즈 건을 내가 맡았어'
They gave me the Karasz oil leases.
잘됐네
That's fantastic.
알고 있었어?
Did you know?
'확실하진 않았지만
린이 언질은 줬었어'
Not for sure.
Lynn might've mentioned something.
데이빗, 당신이 자랑스러워
David, I am very proud of you.
'빨리 가봐야 돼, 결혼식을 할
교회를 보기로 했거든
Look, I've got to go. We're checking out
the church for the wedding...
'대신 점심 때 카페 마루에서 만나'
but I'll meet you for lunch at Cafe Marue.
알았어
Okay.
이건 어디서 났어?
Where the hell did you get these?
오늘 편지가 왔어
In the mail today.
회신 주소나 메모도 없어
No return address, no note, nothing.
데이빗, 우리도 섹시해 보이네
David, we look seriously hot in these.
개판 5분 전처럼 보이겠지
We look like we're in deep shit,
that's what we look like.
이해를 못하겠어
리사가 이걸 어떻게 찍었지?
I don't understand. I mean, how'd she do it?
글쎄, 다른 사람이나...
I don't know.
Maybe someone was there, hiding...
몰래 카메라가 있었겠지
or maybe a camera was planted.
맙소사, 그 괴짜일까?
생각을 해봐, 데이빗
Oh, my God, what if it was the creep?
I mean, think about it, David.
그 여자랑 클럽 얘기도
그 사람이 해줬잖아?
He's the one that told you all about her,
and the club. Remember?
소문이 난다면...
If this kind of thing got out...
- 다른 주문이라도?
- 아뇨
- Can I bring you something?
- No.
적어도 당신은 해링턴 가문이지
At least you're a Harrington.
무슨 뜻이야?
Meaning what?
당신에게 돈은 엄청나잖아
또 당신 아빠가 지켜줄 테고
You got your gazillion-dollar trust fund, and
your daddy's always gonna be there for you.
무슨 소리야, 데이빗?
What are you talking about, David?
날 지켜준 사람은 없었어
I never had anyone protect me.
난 촌구석 출신인데다
어릴 땐 배급을 받아 먹었어
I'm from Wilmington, Delaware.
I grew up on food stamps.
내 아버지?
My father?
일자리 하나 없이
술에 찌든 양반이었어
My father was a fucking drunk
who could never keep a job.
신파는 그만 하시지
Easy on the melodrama.
공화당에 의석을 얻으려고
노력한 거 알지?
You know I've been talking to the Party
about a congressional seat.
카라즈 건이 보증수표야
The Karasz deal could be my ticket out.
그걸 망칠 순 없어
I'm not gonna let this fuck it up.
난 대체 뭐지?
당신의 정치 야망의 도구야?
What am I in this?
Just part of your political ambition?
지금 그런 뜻이야?
Is that what this is all about?
'데이빗이 대사의 딸과 결혼해...
"David marries an ambassador's daughter...
'워싱턴 정가에 가는 길을
몸으로 얻어내다? '
"and scores his big chance
to fuck his way to Washington"?
미안해, 티쉬
I'm sorry. Tish.
그런 뜻으로 한 말은 아니었어
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it the way it sounded.
사랑해, 당신도 알잖아
I love you. You know that.
알았어
Okay.
어쩌면 리사가 기념품으로
보낸 걸지도 모르잖아
Maybe she just sent them
as a souvenir or something.
이 사진의 원본을 찾아야 해
I want whatever these were made from.
테이프든 필름이든 말이야
The tape, the film, whatever.
그걸 어떻게 찾아?
And how do you plan on doing that?
알람브라로 다시 가서
클림과 얘기를 해봐야지
Go back to the Alhambra
and have a little talk with Mr. Klim.
그 사람과 상관이 없다면?
And what if he had nothing to do with it?
리사의 주소라도 알려주겠지
Maybe he can tell us where we can find her.
데이빗...
David...
이런 일을 처리해주는 사람도 있어
we have people who can
take care of this kind of thing.
안 돼
No.
아무에게도 알려선 안 돼
No one will ever know about this...
절대로
ever.
카라즈 채굴권 서류예요
The Karasz oil lease documents...
오늘 오후에 자모스 씨와
회의가 있습니다
and you have that meeting
with Mr. Szamos this afternoon.
도라, 다른 일이 있으니
약속을 취소해줘
Dora, get me out of it.
I have something else I have to do.
네
Okay.
없다는군
He's gone.
새 지배인 말이
며칠 전에 갑자기 그만뒀대
The new manager told me
that he just up and quit the other night.
그를 고용한 회사의
번호를 받아왔어
I got the number of the property
management company that hired him.
어서 타, 가자
Well, get in, let's go.
먼저 저 방을 봐야해
Not till after we get a look at that room.
- 그게 무슨 소용이야?
- 뭔가 찾을지도 몰라
- What good is that gonna do?
- We might find something.
손님 말이야?
Yeah, like guests.
노크해봤지만 아무도 없었어
어서 가자
I knocked. No one's there. Come on.
- 젠장!
- 왜?
- Shit!
- What?
손을 베었어
I cut myself.
이건 미친 짓이야
누군가 소리를 들었을 거야
This is crazy. Someone had to hear that.
- 얼마나 아파?
- 괜찮아
- How bad is it?
- I'll be fine.
이 방을 누군가 쓰고 있어
There's somebody staying here.
데이빗, 내 말 들려?
David, did you hear me?
그 사진 중 하나는
침대 위에서 찍었어
One of the angles was from above the bed.
뭔가 보여?
You see anything?
선이 있어
There's a wire.
받아
Here.
데이빗
David.
카메라야
It's a camera.
돈을 요구하진 않았잖아
No one's asked for any money.
아직은 그렇지
Not yet.
아버지에게 말씀드리는 게 좋겠어
Look, maybe we should just tell my father.
차라리 권총으로
내 머리를 날려버리겠어
I might as well put a gun to my head
and pull the trigger.
녀석이 일했던 회사를
찾아가겠어
We'll go to that company he worked for.
녀석을 찾아서...
I'll find him...
놈이 원하는 걸 주겠어
and we'll give him whatever he wants.
조세프 클림은 더 이상
여기서 일하지 않아요
Josef Klim doesn't work for us, anymore.
- 언제부터요?
- 이틀 됐어요
- Since when?
- Two days ago.
지배인은 집시나 다름없죠
직장에서 먹고 자요
Most managers are rental gypsies.
They live where they work.
제가 아는 주소는
알람브라가 마지막입니다
The Alhambra was his last known residence,
as far as I know.
이게 그 사람의
휴대폰 번호예요
That is his cell phone number.
- 감사합니다
- 천만에요
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
제 명함입니다
소식이 들리면 연락주세요
Here's my card.
If you hear anything, please call.
알았어요
I will.
- 감사합니다
- 천만에요
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
전화를 안 받아
자동응답기도 없어
He's not answering. There's no voice mail.
그럼 기다려야겠네
So we wait.
어쩔 작정인지 보자고
See what they have in mind.
도라를 시켜 이 휴대폰의
주소지를 알아봐야겠어
Maybe I can get Dora
to get a billing address for his cell phone.
그래
Yeah.
이번 일은 미안해, 데이빗
I am so sorry about this, David.
전부 내 잘못이야
This whole thing, it's my fault.
그날 내가 거부할 수도 있었어
I could've said no that night.
재즈가 왜 싫다는지
이해할 수가 없구나
I don't see what you have
against a jazz combo.
엄마, 좀 더 경쾌한 음악을
연주했으면 좋겠어요
Well, Mother, we were hoping
for something a little more upbeat.
난 재즈가 좋아
우리 결혼 때도 재즈를 연주했지
I like jazz. They played jazz at our wedding.
나이 드신 하객은 어쩌라고?
And what about your older wedding guests?
- 알 게 뭐예요
- 페리
- Fuck them.
- Perry.
재즈는 다 싫어해요, 어머니
제 말을 믿어요
No one wants a jazz combo, Mother.
Believe me.
페리 말을 들어요
우리 가족의 예술가잖아요
Listen to Perry.
He is the artiste in the family.
데이빗은 어때?
What do you say, David?
데이빗
David.
뭐라고?
I'm sorry?
어머니가 피로연에
어떤 음악을 쓸지 물어보셨어
Mother wants to know what kind of music
you want at our reception.
그러니까 내 말은 재즈도...
I was just saying how a jazz combo...
재즈가 좋겠습니다
A jazz combo would be great.
데이빗
David.
실례합니다
Excuse me.
- 왔군
- 멋진 파티입니다
- Hey.
- Great party.
- 그래
- 모두 대사님을 그리워하겠죠
- Yeah.
- They're gonna miss you here.
난 아쉬울 것 없네
카라즈 건은 어찌 돼 가나?
Their loss, my gain.
Hey, how's that Karasz thing coming?
늦어지고 있습니다
가려낼 게 많으니까요
Slow. There's a lot to sift through.
조지 자모스 말이
만날 약속을 했는데...
Well, George Szamos said
he set up a meeting with you...
자네가 피했다면서? 왜지?
and you blew him off? What...
그럴 의도는 아니었습니다
I didn't mean to leave him
with that impression.
월요일 아침에
만나 뵙도록 하겠습니다
I'll hook up with him Monday morning.
I promise.
이건 중요한 일이네
This is important, David.
알고 있습니다
실망시켜드리지 않겠습니다
I know, sir. I'm not gonna let you down.
자네가 실망시키는 건 상관없어
I'm not worried about you letting me down.
단지 티쉬가 걱정될 뿐일세
I'm just... I'm kind of concerned about Tish.
데이빗, 난 자네의
능력이 의심스러워
David, I'm not sure you have what it takes.
바시 건을 실패했을 때와...
I mean, you remember
when that Vaci deal fell through...
지난 번 식사 기억나나?
and we had that meeting?
난 아직도 같은 생각이야
자네 눈은 필사적이거든
I still feel the same way, you know.
I still see that desperation in your eyes.
항상 밖에서 내부를
들여다보는 신세로 남겠지
I mean, I think you're always gonna be
on the outside looking in.
자네 잘못은 아니야
It's not your fault.
그건 타고난 거니까
자네 출신이 나빠서 그래
It's this inherent flaw.
It's because of where you come from.
자넨 평생 돈의 힘을
이해하지 못해
You're never going to understand
the power of wealth...
날 때부터 지녔던
보이지 않는 당당함이지
and the subtle guarantees in life
that come with it.
맛을 보고 냄새를 맡고
만져볼 수는 있겠지만...
I mean, you can taste it,
and you can smell it, and you can touch it...
평생 이해할 순 없을 거야
but you're never
really gonna understand it...
필사적으로 원하겠지만
as desperately as you want to.
그런 집착은 실패로 이어지니...
And desperation leads to failure...
난 내 딸에게
실패를 안겨주긴 싫다네
and failure isn't what I had in mind
for my daughter.
하나만 물어볼게
Tell me something, Lynn.
지금 아빠가 얼마나 참으실까?
What's Daddy's pain threshold right now?
무슨 뜻이야?
What do you mean?
있잖아...
You know...
대법원 얘기도 오가고 있으니...
with all the talk about the possible
Supreme Court appointment and all...
어느 정도 화가 나야 폭발하실까?
how much can he take
before he goes ballistic?
무슨 일 있어?
What's wrong?
- 맙소사, 임신했니?
- 아냐
- Oh, my God, are you pregnant?
- No.
- 그럼 문제가 생겼어?
- 아니
- Well, are you in some sort of trouble?
- No.
별일 아니야
Look, it's no big deal, really.
못들은 셈 쳐
Just forget I said anything.
왜?
Hey.
그 생각이 떠나지 않아
I can't stop thinking about it.
괜찮아
It's okay.
해결할 수 있어
방법을 찾을 거야
We'll get through it. We'll find a way.
당신을 망칠까 두렵다는군
He's afraid I'll fail you.
무슨 소리야?
누가 두렵다고?
What are you talking about? Who's afraid?
당신 아버지
Your father.
오늘 밤 피로연에서 아버님이
바시 건을 탓하시면서...
Tonight, at the reception, he reminded me
that he still blames me for the Vaci deal...
내게...
that I don't...
당신 세계에 끼어들...
have what it takes...
능력이 없다고 하시더군
to make it in your world.
웃기지도 않는 권위의식이야
That's just his elite Harrington bullshit.
나도 다 들었던 얘기야
아빤 틀렸어
God. I've heard it all before. He's wrong.
당신을 잘 모르셔
He's wrong about you.
돈과 재력도 과신하시지
He's wrong about money and its power.
그게 부자를 강하게 만드는 거야
That's what makes the rich strong.
부자는 능력이 되니 일하지만...
They do things because they can...
보통 사람들은
필사적으로 일해
when everyone else does them
'cause they have to.
돈은 인생의 보증수표야
Money is the only real guarantee in life.
무슨 일이야, 리처드?
What's up, Richard?
이번엔 개판치지 마
I need for you not to fuck up here.
무슨 소리야?
Meaning what?
해링턴 가문과 결혼했을 때
난 세상을 다 가진 줄 알았어
When I married into the Harringtons,
I thought I owned the world.
하지만 곧 깨달았지
그들과 동화되지 않으면...
It didn't take long to realize
if you're not one of them...
쓸모없는 인간일 뿐이라고
you're not one of anything.
알아
I know.
그럼 혼전계약서에 따라
이혼할 경우엔...
Well, then, you also know the prenup
you're signing leaves you nothing...
무일푼이라는 것도 알겠군
if the marriage doesn't last.
해링턴 가문에선
살아남기가 힘들어
They're hard work, the Harringtons.
많은 시간과 정력을 쏟아도
돌아오는 건 없지
A lot of time and energy invested
with a potential for no payday.
그 대신...
Unless...
그들이 가진 지위를 기회로
잘 이용할 수는 있어
we take advantage of what their position
in life has to offer by way of an opportunity.
카라즈 건은
절호의 기회야, 데이빗
The Karasz leases are a big prize, David.
이건 우리 둘 모두에게...
They could lead to better days...
더 나은 미래를 보장하지
for both of us.
그 휴대폰 번호와 일치하는
주소를 찾아냈어요
I found the address
that matches that cell phone number.
그러니까 내 말은
네 아버지가 걱정하신다는 거야
I was just saying
that your father was a bit concerned...
네가 데이빗의 아파트에서
잠을 자면 보기가 안 좋잖니
about, you know, how it looks when
you stay overnight at David's apartment.
어머니는 전형적인 공화당원이군요
God, you are so Republican.
저건 정말 끔찍해요
That is horrendous.
이탈리아 밀라노의
유명 디자이너 작품이야
It's Italian, from a top designer in Milan.
베르사체 짜가 분위기예요
It's Versace on acid.
언제부터 결혼식 전문가가 되셨나?
When did you become an expert
on wedding dresses?
그래, 자기야
무슨 일이야?
Hey, honey, what's up?
티쉬, 잠깐
Tish. No.
진정해
Calm down.
이건 어떠니?
What about this one, dear?
20만 달러를 원한대
They want $200,000.
부다페스트의
어떤 피씨방에서 온 거야
This came from some Internet cafe in Buda.
경찰에게 알려야겠어
그 사람의 주소도 있으니...
We should tell the police. I mean,
now that you have his address, they...
경찰은 믿을 수 없어
Can't trust the police.
우린 도움이 필요해, 데이빗
We need help, David.
자긴 말도 못하게 하잖아
아빠에게만 말씀드릴게
You won't let me talk to anybody.
Please, let me just go to my father.
리처드가 내 사무실에 와서
카라즈 건을 신신당부하더군
Richard was just in my office
begging me not to screw up the Karasz deal.
아버님은 지금도
날 언짢게 보시는데...
Knowing the way your father feels
about me...
이 사실을 아시면
과연 뭐라고 하실까?
what do you think he would do
if he found out about this?
공화당에서 아버지에게...
Did you know the Party talked to him...
당신 의석에 대해
얘기한 걸 알고 있어?
about endorsing you
for a congressional seat?
돈을 주겠어
I'll pay them.
내 계좌를 털면 충분해
I'll drain my accounts. I have enough.
아니, 내 유산을 쓰자
No, we'll just get it from my trust.
그 돈에 손을 대면
사람들이 의심할 거야
You can't start messing with your trust.
People will start asking questions.
다들 21살 때 지분을 받았으니
아무도 의심 안 할 거야
We all got our shares after we turned 21.
No one would suspect a thing.
아니, 내가 하자는 대로 해
No. Let's just do it my way.
내게도 충분히 있어
I have enough.
우리보고 오라는 공원이
어딘지나 알고 있어?
Do you even know this amusement park
that they want us to go to?
그래, 지금은 폐쇄 중이지
하지만 거긴 나 혼자 가겠어
Yeah, it's been closed down for a while,
but there's no "us." I'm going alone.
그건 안 돼
No, you're not.
우린 함께야
We're in this together.
시간이 지났어
It's past time.
시험일지도 몰라
Maybe it's some sort of test.
경찰을 데려왔는지
확인하려고 말이야
You know,
see if we brought the police or anything.
- 총은 왜 가져왔어?
- 녀석이 안 오면 내가 찾겠어
- Why'd you bring your gun?
- Lf he doesn't come to us, we'll go to him.
- 데이빗, 내 말 들려?
- 그래
- David, did you hear me?
- Yeah, I heard you.
- 필요할 것 같아서 가져왔어
- 난 싫어
- I brought it 'cause I thought I might need it.
- Well, I don't like it.
나도 마찬가지야
Neither do I.
천천히 꺼내
Take it out very slowly.
땅에 내려놔
Put it on the ground.
좋아
Good.
그게 돈인가?
Is that the money?
그래
Yes.
당신이 가져와
You. Bring it to me.
우리에게 넘겨줄 물건은?
What about what we're buying with it?
받게 될 거야
You will get it.
- 언제?
- 곧
- When?
- Soon.
멍청한 짓 하면 사람이 다쳐!
Don't do anything stupid
and no one gets hurt!
데이빗
David.
시키는 대로 해
Just do as he says.
저 녀석 말대로 해
Just do what he says.
난 여길 나갈 테니...
I'm walking out of here...
넌 거기 그대로 있어
and you stay right where you are.
내가 차에 탄 다음
여자를 보내주지
When I get to the car I let her go.
날 막으려 하면
여자는 죽은 목숨이야
You do anything to stop me and she's dead.
데이빗!
David!
- 티쉬
- 여기야
- Tish.
- Here.
- 괜찮아?
- 그런 것 같아
- You okay?
- I think so.
어디로 갔지?
Where'd he go?
저 위야
He's up there.
물건을 내놔!
Give me what I fucking paid for!
엎드려!
Get down!
- 그냥 보내줘!
- 평생 모은 돈이라고!
- Let him go!
- That's my life savings!
맙소사
Oh, God.
젠장
Shit.
데이빗!
David!
불안해
I don't like this.
여기서 기다려
Stay here.
봐, 그 사람이야
Look, it's him.
죽었어
He's dead.
무서워, 데이빗
I'm scared, David.
이젠 섹스 비디오가 문제가 아냐
This isn't about us fucking on some video.
살인이라고
It's murder.
협박이 살인 사건이 됐어
We've gone from blackmail to murder.
내가 대사관에서 처음 일할 때
곤란한 상황에 처했던...
There was this guy I did some work for
when I first started with the Embassy...
미국인을 도와준 적이 있어
an American
who got himself into some trouble.
그가 도움이 될 거야
He might be able to help.
얼굴은 낯이 익지만
확실히는 모르겠군요
Her face looks familiar,
but it don't ring no bells.
그녀를 찾으려면
어떻게 해야합니까?
How would we go about looking for her?
만약 매춘부라면
먼저 거리를 훑어봐야죠
If she's pussy for hire,
I'd start by hitting the streets.
스트립 클럽, 매춘 클럽도
Strip joints, fuck clubs, peepshows.
도움이 될 만한 곳도
몇 군데 있습니다
There are a couple of places
that might be able to help you.
전 여자를 수소문해 보죠
In the meantime, I'll make a few calls.
- 그 여자 이름이 뭐라고요?
- 리사, 가명이 아니라면요
- What was her name again?
- Risa. If that's her real name.
지저분한 일인데 괜찮겠습니까?
Are you sure you want to mess with this?
수고해주시면 고맙겠군요
I'd appreciate it if you made the calls.
걱정 마십시오
이유나 이름도 묻지 않겠소
It's done.
No questions asked and no names.
신세 갚으려면 아직 멀었죠
I still owe you a big one.
실례합니다, 이 여자 알아요?
Excuse me, you know her?
이름은 리사입니다
Her name is Risa.
스트립 쇼
'영어 합니까?
Do you speak English?
'이 여자 알아요?
Do you know her?
'사람을 찾고 있어요
I'm looking for someone.
'만약 매춘부라면
먼저 거리를 훑어봐야죠
If she's pussy for hire,
I'd start by hitting the streets.
'스트립 클럽, 매춘 클럽도'
Strip joints, fuck clubs, peepshows.
섹스 숍
'지저분한 일인데 괜찮겠습니까? '
Are you sure you want to mess with this?
이 여자 아세요?
머리는 갈색입니다
Do you know her? She has brown hair.
시간만 아깝게
You waste my time.
가자
Let's go.